[
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "What was the code name for the &quot;Nintendo Gamecube&quot;?",
    "correct_answer": "Dolphin",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Nitro",
      "Revolution",
      "Atlantis"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which of these features was added in the 1994 game &quot;Heretic&quot; that the original &quot;DOOM&quot; could not add due to limitations?",
    "correct_answer": "Looking up and down",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Increased room sizes",
      "Unlimited weapons",
      "Highly-detailed textures"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What was the first video game in the Batman &quot;Arkham&quot; series?",
    "correct_answer": "Arkham Asylum",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Arkham Knight",
      "Arkham City",
      "Arkham Origins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which video game was recalled for containing a hidden, playable South Park episode?",
    "correct_answer": "Tiger Woods 99 PGA Tour",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Tony Hawk&#039;s Pro Skater 3",
      "Sonic Adventure",
      "Madden 99"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Excluding their instructor, how many members of Class VII are there in the game &quot;Legend of Heroes: Trails of Cold Steel&quot;?",
    "correct_answer": "9",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "6",
      "10",
      "3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "In the Gamecube Version of &quot;Resident Evil&quot; what text document is open on the monitor of the computer in the Visual Data Room?",
    "correct_answer": "A GDC Document",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Text Document on Herbs",
      "Nothing",
      "Document on B.O.Ws"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "There are 6 legendary cards in &quot;Clash Royale&quot;.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "In the original &quot;Super Mario Bros.&quot;, what is the acceleration of Mario if he was in free fall?",
    "correct_answer": "91.28 m/s^2",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "110  m/s^2",
      "9.42  m/s^2",
      "4.4  m/s^2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "What is the name of the final boss in Turok: Dinosaur Hunter?",
    "correct_answer": "The Campaigner",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "The Primagen",
      "Oblivion",
      "Lord Tyrannus"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "When was the first &quot;Half-Life&quot; released?",
    "correct_answer": "1998",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "2004",
      "1999",
      "1997"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "In &quot;Sonic the Hedgehog 3&quot; for the Sega Genesis, what is the color of the second Chaos Emerald you can get from Special Stages?",
    "correct_answer": "Orange",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Blue",
      "Green",
      "Magenta"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Niko Bellic is the protagonist of Grand Theft Auto IV.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "When was the game &#039;Portal 2&#039; released?",
    "correct_answer": "2011",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "2014",
      "2009",
      "2007"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "In Left 4 Dead, what is the name of the Special Infected that is unplayable in Versus mode?",
    "correct_answer": "The Witch",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "The Tank",
      "The Smoker",
      "The Spitter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "In &quot;Overwatch,&quot; an allied McCree will say &quot;Step right up&quot; upon using his ultimate ability Deadeye.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Who is the creator of the Super Smash Bros. Series?",
    "correct_answer": "Masahiro Sakurai",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Reggie Fils-Aim&eacute;",
      "Bill Trinen",
      "Hideo Kojima"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "In what Half-Life expansion can you find Gordon&#039;s picture in an &quot;Employee of the Month&quot; picture frame?",
    "correct_answer": "Half-Life: Opposing Force",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Half-Life: Blue Shift",
      "Half-Life: Decay",
      "They Hunger"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Danganronpa 2: Goodbye Despair featured all of the surviving students from the first game.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "In PROTOTYPE 2. who is referred to as &quot;Tango Primary&quot;?",
    "correct_answer": "James Heller",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Alex Mercer",
      "Dana Mercer",
      "Any Goliaths roaming around"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which is not a playable character in the 2005 video game Killer7?",
    "correct_answer": "Frank Smith",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Mask de Smith",
      "Dan Smith",
      "Coyote Smith"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "In Danganronpa: Trigger Happy Havoc, what is the protagonist&#039;s name?",
    "correct_answer": "Makoto Naegi",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Hajime Hinata",
      "Nagito Komaeda",
      "Komaru Naegi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What was the world&#039;s first handheld game device?",
    "correct_answer": "Mattel Auto Race",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Game Boy",
      "Microvision",
      "Game &amp; Watch"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Which water-type Pok&eacute;mon starter was introduced in the 4th generation of the series?",
    "correct_answer": "Piplup",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Totodile",
      "Oshawott",
      "Mudkip"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "The names of Tom Nook&#039;s cousins in the Animal Crossing franchise are named &quot;Timmy&quot; and &quot;Jimmy&quot;.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which of these Pok&eacute;mon cannot learn Surf?",
    "correct_answer": "Arbok",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Linoone",
      "Tauros",
      "Nidoking"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "In Hitman: Blood Money, what is the name of the target in the mission &quot;Death of a Showman&quot;?",
    "correct_answer": "Joseph Clarence",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "The Swing King",
      "Maynard John",
      "Manuel Delgado"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "The default playermodel of Garry&#039;s Mod is this Half Life 2 character.",
    "correct_answer": "Isaac Kleiner",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "G-Man",
      "Alyx Vance",
      "Gordon Freeman"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What do the video games No Man&rsquo;s Sky and Mighty No. 9 have in common?",
    "correct_answer": "Both were announced in 2013.",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Both were crowdfunded.",
      "Both were developed by indie studios.",
      "Both were released for the PlayStation 3."
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Mortal Kombat was almost based on Jean-Claude Van Damme movie.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "In Riot Games &quot;League of Legends&quot; the name of Halloween event is called &quot;The Reckoning&quot;.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "How many voice channels does the Super Nintendo Entertainment System support?",
    "correct_answer": "8",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "6",
      "10",
      "12"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "&quot;Gimmick!&quot; is a Japanese Famicom game that uses a sound chip expansion in the cartridge. What is it called?",
    "correct_answer": "FME-7",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "VRC7",
      "VRC6",
      "MMC5"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "What was the first Call of Duty game to include the Zombies gamemode?",
    "correct_answer": "Call of Duty: World at War",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Call of Duty: Black Ops",
      "Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 2",
      "Call of Duty: Black Ops III"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which of the following Copy Abilities was only featured in &quot;Kirby &amp; The Amazing Mirror&quot;?",
    "correct_answer": "Mini",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Magic",
      "Smash",
      "Missile"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Who is the main protagonist in Danganronpa 2: Goodbye Despair?",
    "correct_answer": "Hajime Hinata",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Nagito Komaeda",
      "Makoto Naegi",
      "Junko Enoshima"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which variant of the MP5 is depicted in Counter-Strike 1.6?",
    "correct_answer": "MP5N",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "MP5SD",
      "MP5K",
      "MP5RAS"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "What is not a playable race in &quot;Final Fantasy XIV: A Realm Reborn&quot;?",
    "correct_answer": "Hume",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Miqo&#039;te",
      "Lalafell",
      "Roegadyn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "In &quot;Call Of Duty: Zombies&quot;, which weapon does NOT deal any damage?",
    "correct_answer": "31-79 JGb215",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Sliquifier",
      "V-R11",
      "Wunderwaffe DG-2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "The ghosts in &quot;Pac-Man&quot; and &quot;Ms. Pac-Man&quot; have completely different behavior.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "The game &quot;Pocket Morty&quot; has a Morty called &quot;Pocket Mortys Morty&quot;?",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "In the Halo series, which era of SPARTAN is Master Chief? ",
    "correct_answer": "SPARTAN-II",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "SPARTAN-I",
      "SPARTAN-III",
      "SPARTAN-IV"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "What is the main character&#039;s name in &quot;Braid&quot;?",
    "correct_answer": "Tim",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Boregard",
      "James",
      "Jackson"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "In &quot;Need for Speed III: Hot Pursuit&quot;, what is the name of the fictional car?",
    "correct_answer": "El Ni&ntilde;o",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "R&aacute;pido",
      "&Aacute;gil",
      "La Ni&ntilde;a"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "In the Kingdom Hearts series, which is not an optional boss you can fight?",
    "correct_answer": "Master Yen Sid",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Sephiroth",
      "Julius",
      "Kurt Zisa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Who is credited with having created the world&#039;s first video game Easter Egg?",
    "correct_answer": "Warren Robinett",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Julius Smith",
      "Will Crowther",
      "Don Woods"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "What character is NOT apart of the Grand Theft Auto series?",
    "correct_answer": "Michael Cardenas",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Packie McReary",
      "Tommy Vercetti",
      "Lester Crest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "In &quot;Kingdom Hearts&quot;, what mission are Donald and Goofy assigned by King Mickey?",
    "correct_answer": "To find the Key bearer and stick with him!",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "To find the Key bearer and steal the key!",
      "To find the Key bearer and report back!",
      "To find the Key bearer and kill him!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Which of the following games has the largest map size?",
    "correct_answer": "Just Cause 2",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Grand Theft Auto 5",
      "The Elder Scrolls 4:  Oblivion",
      "The Witcher 3:  Wild Hunt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "In Fallout: New Vegas, which one of these casinos can you not play in?",
    "correct_answer": "Lucky 38",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "The Tops",
      "Gammorah",
      "Ultra-Luxe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Rincewind from the 1995 Discworld game was voiced by which member of Monty Python?",
    "correct_answer": "Eric Idle",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "John Cleese",
      "Terry Gilliam",
      "Michael Palin"
    ]
  }
]
